01). Load a game (for the system you are adding).
02). Type in the "...enter rom filename..." field, the exact filename of the loaded game without extension. WARING - Case sensetive.
- For Sony Playstation 1 and 2 games, the filename should actually be the game's SLES/SLUS/SCUS/SLPS... code, and looks like "SCUS-94163". "Retrieving romname mode" should be set to "fixed length = 10"
- For Nintendo GameCube and Wii games, look in the dolphin game properties, and on the "info" tab find "Game ID" field. It should looks like "GENE69" for example. "Retrieving romname mode" should be set to "fixed length = 6"
03). Click "search"
04). Select first row, and click "Search pointer to selected".
05). Find pointers to firsts 3 - 5 rows.
06). CLOSE the emulator, then reopen it.
07). Load another game (but for the same system).
08). Type in the field new filename (or just find it in "Value" column, and double-click on the row), and press "UPDATE" button.
09). Repeat steps from 06 to 08, 2-3 times.


*After copleting theese steps, it is recommended to save the found addreses to the preset, by RIGHT-clicking any number to the left of the addres table.
*By left-clicking on the number, you can load the preset to choose another addres later.

10). If you are finding Sony PS1/PS2 game name, choose "Fixed Length" option, and set it to 10.
     If you are finding GameCube/Wii Pgame name, choose "Fixed Length" option, and set it to 5.
11). Choose any row in the table. If this row contains you romname with extension, check "Remove Extension" checkbox.
Click next.