1). Load a game for the system you are adding and wait until it is completely loaded.
2). Press "Currently playing this system" button.
3). Load a game for another system.
4). Press "Currently playing other system" button.
5). Repaet steps 3-4 for each emulated system.
6). CLOSE emulator completely, than reopen it.
7). Repeat steps 1-5 to make sure the system is recognized correctly.

*After copleting theese steps, it is recommended to save the found addreses to the preset, by RIGHT-clicking any number to the left of the addres table.
*By left-clicking on the number, you can load the preset to choose another addres later.

8). Choose any adress in the table, and click next.