Here you set emulator options. They are quiet self explanatory.

The "EXE" and "CRC" fields identifies your emulator, and filled automatically.

The "Version" field is just for your information, it is not required to fill it, by highly recommended.
If your modify existing emulator settings, the "Version" field is filled automatically.

Select the "Pause" field, and press pause button used in emulator. Some display methods require the emulator to be paused to display cheats menu correctly.

Select system emulated by the emulator. If the emulator emulate multiple systems, you should go through the entire process for each emulated system that you want to add.

Select "The emulated system can be determined by emulator window title" option, if the emulated system is somehow displayed in the emulator main window title, than type in "Title should contain" field, something, that is displayed in the emulator title only when the system you are adding is emulated. This field is case sensetive.

Select "The emulated system can only be determined by memory address" option, if there is no information about emulated system in the emu title.

"Rom name can be obtained from emulator window title" should be checked, if the game name can be extracted from the emulator window title.