  In general, you use emulator's built-in cheats to set emulated system's ram to specific value, than search it withing this tab.


  If an emulator have no built in cheats, you have to find somewhere a cheat, that affect at least two bytes, and set them to known value. i.e. score cheat. Then, when you play, get a little score, then find it and apply offset.
  For example in MESS, I found Sega GameGear 0 addr with this cheat for "Dr. Robotnik's Mean Bean Machine":

  FAKE Score (One's Digit) : 00CC-D809
  FAKE Score (Ten's Digit) : 00CC-D709
  FAKE Score (Hundred's Digit) : 00CC-D609
  FAKE Score (Thousand's Digit) : 00CC-D509
  FAKE Score (Ten-Thousand's Digit) : 00CC-D409
  FAKE Score (Hundred-Thousand's Digit) : 00CC-D309

  In gamegear cheat format 00CC-D709, means "write value 09 to adress CCD7". Play a game a couple of minutes to get a little score. For example, you will end up with 637 score points. As we can see in cheats, each (decimal) digit in score = 1byte in memory. So search for 00060307. You will find address CCD5 of emulated handheld.
  Gamegear memory begins at C000, so in emulator this will be 0 address. But cheat parser need to know the REAL 0 addr, so the next step is enter "CD5" (and not "CCD5") in "offset in emulated system" field, and click "ajust offset", to get C000 address of emulated system. Than use "hexSubstract" in additional actions with value "C000".

  Use system specific info, on the right tab of this page to get more details.
