NES use at least two rams, 0x0000 - 0x0800 (main ram), and 0x6000+ for cartrige ram. It can be used too, so you have to find both.

With FCEUX you can't search ram using cheats, use Tools/Ramsearch, find an unusual pattern (if you will search for "01020304" you will find yourself with thousands of entries), then search for it, and ajust offset if needed.

For dolphin use cheats, AR-codes like:
04000000 050367AB
04000004 070988CD
then search for "050367AB070988CD" This will be your 0 address.

For pscx2 create .pnach file with something like this inside:
patch=1,EE,20200000,word,05F5E0F3
call it the crc of your game (can be found in pcsx2 console, when the game is loaded), and search for "05F5E0F3".
Then ajust offset - 200000.


In N64 use cheat like
81000000 4433
81000002 2211
then search for 11223344 because it rotate bytes.
In project64 v2, deactivate and activate cheat, to take it in accaunt.