  NES use at least two rams, 0x0000 - 0x0800 (main ram), and 0x6000+ for cartrige ram. In emulators, they could be separated. Cartrige ram can be used for some cheats too, so you have to find them both.

  With FCEUX you can't search ram using cheats, it does not update emulated ram, instead, the cheat values are stored elsewhere. Use Tools/Ramsearch, set "Data Type / Display Mode" to "Hexadecimal", find an unusual pattern (if you will search for "01020304" you will find yourself with thousands of entries), then search for it.

  For example, in Ram search tools you will see "1ec37f1c" at addres 0x35f.
  - Pause the emulator, to prevent value to change.
  - Type "1ec37f1c" into "Enter value to search..." box and click search. 
  - Close and reopen emulator, load any game, then press pause again.
  - With Ram Search tool, look the pattern you now have in 0x35f.
  - Change the pattern in Emulator config wizard, and click "RECHECK".
  - Enter 35f in the offset field, and click "Adjust Offset".
